~@~@~@~@~@~@~@~@~ START OF ERRORLOG FOR 2021-08-26 ~@~@~@~@~@~@~@~@~====================================================
     Date: 2021-08-26     Time: 09:32
====================================================
loaded global params
{'SCREEN_W': 1024, 'SCREEN_H': 768, 'CURSOR_VISIBLE': True, 'RESTRICT_SCREEN': True, 'AUTOSHAPING': True, 'TIME_TO_AUTOSHAPE': 10, 'STIMULI_COLORS': 'normal', 'HOST_CONNECTED': True, 'RFID_READER_CONNECTED': False, 'DRO_DURATION': 1, 'REWARD_TYPE': 'pellet', 'REWARD_AMOUNT': 1, 'DEBUG_WINDOW_ON': True}
loaded monkey params
{'H049': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/31/1999', 'LeftWrist': '989001000000000', 'RightWrist': '989001000000000', 'Room': '507.01', 'PiSystem': '103', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, 'H055': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '6/3/1999', 'LeftWrist': '989001000000000', 'RightWrist': '989001000000000', 'Room': '507.01', 'PiSystem': '103', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, 'H033': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/24/1999', 'LeftWrist': '989001000000000', 'RightWrist': '989001000000000', 'Room': '507.01', 'PiSystem': '103', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, 'J860': {'Sex': 'M', 'DOB': '5/23/1997', 'LeftWrist': '989001000000000', 'RightWrist': '982092000000000', 'Room': '507.01', 'PiSystem': '103', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, 'J989': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '4/28/1999', 'LeftWrist': '982091000000000', 'RightWrist': '982091000000000', 'Room': '507.01', 'PiSystem': '103', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, '3-183': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '7/25/2003', 'LeftWrist': '989001000000000', 'RightWrist': '989001000000000', 'Room': '507.02', 'PiSystem': '102', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, '4-238': {'Sex': 'M', 'DOB': '10/14/2004', 'LeftWrist': '989001000000000', 'RightWrist': '982091000000000', 'Room': '507.02', 'PiSystem': '102', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, '5-113': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '6/16/2005', 'LeftWrist': '989001000000000', 'RightWrist': '989001000000000', 'Room': '507.02', 'PiSystem': '102', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, '7-225': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '9/25/2007', 'LeftWrist': '989001000000000', 'RightWrist': '989001000000000', 'Room': '507.02', 'PiSystem': '102', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, 'J719': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '3/23/1997', 'LeftWrist': '982091000000000', 'RightWrist': '982091000000000', 'Room': '507.02', 'PiSystem': '102', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, 'J939': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '6/13/1998', 'LeftWrist': '989001000000000', 'RightWrist': '989001000000000', 'Room': '507.02', 'PiSystem': '102', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, '4-148': {'Sex': 'M', 'DOB': '6/17/2004', 'LeftWrist': '989001000000000', 'RightWrist': '982091000000000', 'Room': '507.03', 'PiSystem': '105', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, 'H063': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '6/10/1999', 'LeftWrist': '989001000000000', 'RightWrist': '989001000000000', 'Room': '507.03', 'PiSystem': '105', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, 'H415': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '7/15/2001', 'LeftWrist': '989001000000000', 'RightWrist': '989001000000000', 'Room': '507.03', 'PiSystem': '105', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, '3-091': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/22/2003', 'LeftWrist': '989001000000000', 'RightWrist': '989001000000000', 'Room': '507.03', 'PiSystem': '105', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, 'J729': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '3/31/1997', 'LeftWrist': '982091000000000', 'RightWrist': '982091000000000', 'Room': '507.03', 'PiSystem': '105', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, '10-017': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '4/15/2010', 'LeftWrist': '989001000000000', 'RightWrist': '989001000000000', 'Room': '507.04', 'PiSystem': '104', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, '14-069': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '6/7/2014', 'LeftWrist': '989001000000000', 'RightWrist': '989001000000000', 'Room': '507.04', 'PiSystem': '104', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, '6-088': {'Sex': 'M', 'DOB': '6/9/2006', 'LeftWrist': '989001000000000', 'RightWrist': '982091000000000', 'Room': '507.04', 'PiSystem': '104', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, '9-105': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/28/2009', 'LeftWrist': '989001000000000', 'RightWrist': '989001000000000', 'Room': '507.04', 'PiSystem': '104', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, 'J743': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '4/12/1997', 'LeftWrist': '982091000000000', 'RightWrist': '982091000000000', 'Room': '507.04', 'PiSystem': '104', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, '10-193': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '10/12/2010', 'LeftWrist': '989001000000000', 'RightWrist': '989001000000000', 'Room': '507.05', 'PiSystem': '106', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, '12-073': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/26/2012', 'LeftWrist': '989001000000000', 'RightWrist': '989001000000000', 'Room': '507.05', 'PiSystem': '106', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, 'J436': {'Sex': 'M', 'DOB': '4/11/1993', 'LeftWrist': '989001000000000', 'RightWrist': '982091000000000', 'Room': '507.05', 'PiSystem': '106', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, '5-201': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '8/18/2005', 'LeftWrist': '989001000000000', 'RightWrist': '989001000000000', 'Room': '507.05', 'PiSystem': '106', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, 'J721': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '3/27/1997', 'LeftWrist': '982091000000000', 'RightWrist': '982091000000000', 'Room': '507.05', 'PiSystem': '106', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, '11-163': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '7/15/2011', 'LeftWrist': '989001000000000', 'RightWrist': '989001000000000', 'Room': '507.06', 'PiSystem': '107', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, '13-014': {'Sex': 'M', 'DOB': '3/4/2013', 'LeftWrist': '989001000000000', 'RightWrist': '982091000000000', 'Room': '507.06', 'PiSystem': '107', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, 'J857': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '4/5/1998', 'LeftWrist': '982091000000000', 'RightWrist': '982091000000000', 'Room': '507.06', 'PiSystem': '107', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, '13-029': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '4/14/2013', 'LeftWrist': '989001000000000', 'RightWrist': '989001000000000', 'Room': '507.07', 'PiSystem': '109 & 110', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, '5-069': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/26/2005', 'LeftWrist': '989001000000000', 'RightWrist': '989001000000000', 'Room': '507.07', 'PiSystem': '109 & 110', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, '8-069': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/15/2008', 'LeftWrist': '989001000000000', 'RightWrist': '989001000000000', 'Room': '507.07', 'PiSystem': '109 & 110', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, 'H425': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '10/4/2001', 'LeftWrist': '982091000000000', 'RightWrist': '982091000000000', 'Room': '507.07', 'PiSystem': '109 & 110', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, 'J487': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/15/1994', 'LeftWrist': '982091000000000', 'RightWrist': '982091000000000', 'Room': '507.07', 'PiSystem': '109 & 110', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, 'J904': {'Sex': 'M', 'DOB': '2/15/1998', 'LeftWrist': '989001000000000', 'RightWrist': '982091000000000', 'Room': '507.07', 'PiSystem': '109 & 110', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, 'FISH1': {'Sex': 'NA', 'DOB': 'NA', 'LeftWrist': '989002000000000', 'RightWrist': '989002000000000', 'Room': 'NA', 'PiSystem': 'NA', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, 'FISH2': {'Sex': 'NA', 'DOB': 'NA', 'LeftWrist': '989002000000000', 'RightWrist': '0', 'Room': 'NA', 'PiSystem': 'NA', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, 'MICHELE1': {'Sex': 'NA', 'DOB': 'NA', 'LeftWrist': '989001000000000', 'RightWrist': '989001000000000', 'Room': 'NA', 'PiSystem': 'NA', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, 'MICHELE2': {'Sex': 'NA', 'DOB': 'NA', 'LeftWrist': '982091000000000', 'RightWrist': '982091000000000', 'Room': 'NA', 'PiSystem': 'NA', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}, 'GROUP': {'Sex': 'NA', 'DOB': 'NA', 'LeftWrist': '999999999999999', 'RightWrist': '999999999999999', 'Room': 'NA', 'PiSystem': 'NA', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq-DMTS', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTSsamplevisible': 'TRUE', 'MTSmatches': '1', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85'}}
Screen loaded
743 clipart loaded in 0.768 seconds
Error starting program for GROUP

Traceback (most recent call last):
  File "C:/Users/YLab/Downloads/ww_programs/rhesus-pygames/2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain_frontend.py", line 217, in main
    experiment.new_trial()
  File "C:\Users\YLab\Downloads\ww_programs\rhesus-pygames\2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain\MonkeyTrain\_modules\MTS.py", line 65, in new_trial
    (self.sample_x, self.sample_y) = (int((self.g_params['SAMPLE_W'] - self.stim_size) / 2),
KeyError: 'SAMPLE_W'

Traceback (most recent call last):
  File "C:/Users/YLab/Downloads/ww_programs/rhesus-pygames/2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain_frontend.py", line 217, in main
    experiment.new_trial()
  File "C:\Users\YLab\Downloads\ww_programs\rhesus-pygames\2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain\MonkeyTrain\_modules\MTS.py", line 65, in new_trial
    (self.sample_x, self.sample_y) = (int((self.g_params['SAMPLE_W'] - self.stim_size) / 2),
KeyError: 'SAMPLE_W'

During handling of the above exception, another exception occurred:

Traceback (most recent call last):
  File "C:/Users/YLab/Downloads/ww_programs/rhesus-pygames/2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain_frontend.py", line 315, in <module>
    frontend.main()
  File "C:/Users/YLab/Downloads/ww_programs/rhesus-pygames/2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain_frontend.py", line 221, in main
    sys.exit()
SystemExit

====================================================
     Date: 2021-08-26     Time: 09:35
====================================================
Loaded global params ::

Traceback (most recent call last):
  File "C:/Users/YLab/Downloads/ww_programs/rhesus-pygames/2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain_frontend.py", line 314, in <module>
    frontend = FrontEnd()
  File "C:/Users/YLab/Downloads/ww_programs/rhesus-pygames/2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain_frontend.py", line 50, in __init__
    for k, v in self.g_params:
ValueError: too many values to unpack (expected 2)

====================================================
     Date: 2021-08-26     Time: 09:38
====================================================
Loaded global params ::
SCREEN_W :: 1024
SCREEN_H :: 768
CURSOR_VISIBLE :: True
RESTRICT_SCREEN :: True
AUTOSHAPING :: True
TIME_TO_AUTOSHAPE :: 10
STIMULI_COLORS :: normal
HOST_CONNECTED :: True
RFID_READER_CONNECTED :: False
DRO_DURATION :: 1
REWARD_TYPE :: pellet
REWARD_AMOUNT :: 1
DEBUG_WINDOW_ON :: True
Loaded monkey params
Screen loaded
743 clipart loaded in 0.421 seconds

Traceback (most recent call last):
  File "C:/Users/YLab/Downloads/ww_programs/rhesus-pygames/2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain_frontend.py", line 315, in <module>
    frontend.main()
  File "C:/Users/YLab/Downloads/ww_programs/rhesus-pygames/2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain_frontend.py", line 239, in main
    status = experiment.on_touch(touch_x=touch_x, touch_y=touch_y)
  File "C:\Users\YLab\Downloads\ww_programs\rhesus-pygames\2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain\MonkeyTrain\_modules\MTS.py", line 87, in on_touch
    self.match = Stimulus(size=self.stim_size, pos=self.pos[self.sample_pos], image=self.sample_i)
  File "C:\Users\YLab\Downloads\ww_programs\rhesus-pygames\2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain\MonkeyTrain\_modules\pgtools.py", line 108, in __init__
    self.image = pg.transform.scale(self.image, (size, size))
TypeError: argument 1 must be pygame.Surface, not None

====================================================
     Date: 2021-08-26     Time: 09:40
====================================================
Loaded global params ::
SCREEN_W :: 1024
SCREEN_H :: 768
CURSOR_VISIBLE :: True
RESTRICT_SCREEN :: True
AUTOSHAPING :: True
TIME_TO_AUTOSHAPE :: 10
STIMULI_COLORS :: normal
HOST_CONNECTED :: True
RFID_READER_CONNECTED :: False
DRO_DURATION :: 1
REWARD_TYPE :: pellet
REWARD_AMOUNT :: 1
DEBUG_WINDOW_ON :: True
Loaded monkey params
Screen loaded
743 clipart loaded in 0.447 seconds
pellet
User quit the program

Traceback (most recent call last):
  File "C:/Users/YLab/Downloads/ww_programs/rhesus-pygames/2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain_frontend.py", line 315, in <module>
    frontend.main()
  File "C:/Users/YLab/Downloads/ww_programs/rhesus-pygames/2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain_frontend.py", line 234, in main
    check_quit(event=event)
  File "C:\Users\YLab\Downloads\ww_programs\rhesus-pygames\2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain\MonkeyTrain\_modules\pgtools.py", line 153, in check_quit
    raise SystemExit
SystemExit

====================================================
     Date: 2021-08-26     Time: 11:27
====================================================
Loaded global params ::
SCREEN_W :: 1024
SCREEN_H :: 768
CURSOR_VISIBLE :: True
RESTRICT_SCREEN :: True
AUTOSHAPING :: True
TIME_TO_AUTOSHAPE :: 10
STIMULI_COLORS :: normal
HOST_CONNECTED :: True
RFID_READER_CONNECTED :: False
DRO_DURATION :: 1
REWARD_TYPE :: pellet
REWARD_AMOUNT :: 1
DEBUG_WINDOW_ON :: True
Loaded monkey params
Screen loaded
743 clipart loaded in 0.431 seconds
Error starting program for GROUP

Traceback (most recent call last):
  File "C:/Users/YLab/Downloads/ww_programs/rhesus-pygames/2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain_frontend.py", line 219, in main
    experiment.new_trial()
  File "C:\Users\YLab\Downloads\ww_programs\rhesus-pygames\2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain\MonkeyTrain\_modules\MTSseq.py", line 63, in new_trial
    self.stim_size = int(self.m_params[self.monkey_name]['MTSseqsize'])        # get stim_size
KeyError: 'MTSseqsize'

Traceback (most recent call last):
  File "C:/Users/YLab/Downloads/ww_programs/rhesus-pygames/2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain_frontend.py", line 219, in main
    experiment.new_trial()
  File "C:\Users\YLab\Downloads\ww_programs\rhesus-pygames\2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain\MonkeyTrain\_modules\MTSseq.py", line 63, in new_trial
    self.stim_size = int(self.m_params[self.monkey_name]['MTSseqsize'])        # get stim_size
KeyError: 'MTSseqsize'

During handling of the above exception, another exception occurred:

Traceback (most recent call last):
  File "C:/Users/YLab/Downloads/ww_programs/rhesus-pygames/2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain_frontend.py", line 317, in <module>
    frontend.main()
  File "C:/Users/YLab/Downloads/ww_programs/rhesus-pygames/2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain_frontend.py", line 223, in main
    sys.exit()
SystemExit

====================================================
     Date: 2021-08-26     Time: 11:39
====================================================
Loaded global params ::
SCREEN_W :: 1024
SCREEN_H :: 768
CURSOR_VISIBLE :: True
RESTRICT_SCREEN :: True
AUTOSHAPING :: True
TIME_TO_AUTOSHAPE :: 10
STIMULI_COLORS :: normal
HOST_CONNECTED :: True
RFID_READER_CONNECTED :: False
DRO_DURATION :: 1
REWARD_TYPE :: pellet
REWARD_AMOUNT :: 1
DEBUG_WINDOW_ON :: True
Loaded monkey params
Screen loaded
743 clipart loaded in 0.469 seconds
pellet
User quit the program

Traceback (most recent call last):
  File "C:/Users/YLab/Downloads/ww_programs/rhesus-pygames/2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain_frontend.py", line 317, in <module>
    frontend.main()
  File "C:/Users/YLab/Downloads/ww_programs/rhesus-pygames/2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain_frontend.py", line 236, in main
    check_quit(event=event)
  File "C:\Users\YLab\Downloads\ww_programs\rhesus-pygames\2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain\MonkeyTrain\_modules\pgtools.py", line 153, in check_quit
    raise SystemExit
SystemExit

====================================================
     Date: 2021-08-26     Time: 11:42
====================================================
Loaded global params ::
SCREEN_W :: 1024
SCREEN_H :: 768
CURSOR_VISIBLE :: True
RESTRICT_SCREEN :: True
AUTOSHAPING :: True
TIME_TO_AUTOSHAPE :: 10
STIMULI_COLORS :: normal
HOST_CONNECTED :: True
RFID_READER_CONNECTED :: False
DRO_DURATION :: 1
REWARD_TYPE :: pellet
REWARD_AMOUNT :: 1
DEBUG_WINDOW_ON :: True
Loaded monkey params
Screen loaded
743 clipart loaded in 0.445 seconds
pellet
User quit the program

Traceback (most recent call last):
  File "C:/Users/YLab/Downloads/ww_programs/rhesus-pygames/2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain_frontend.py", line 317, in <module>
    frontend.main()
  File "C:/Users/YLab/Downloads/ww_programs/rhesus-pygames/2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain_frontend.py", line 236, in main
    check_quit(event=event)
  File "C:\Users\YLab\Downloads\ww_programs\rhesus-pygames\2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain\MonkeyTrain\_modules\pgtools.py", line 153, in check_quit
    raise SystemExit
SystemExit

====================================================
     Date: 2021-08-26     Time: 11:42
====================================================
Loaded global params ::
SCREEN_W :: 1024
SCREEN_H :: 768
CURSOR_VISIBLE :: True
RESTRICT_SCREEN :: True
AUTOSHAPING :: True
TIME_TO_AUTOSHAPE :: 10
STIMULI_COLORS :: normal
HOST_CONNECTED :: True
RFID_READER_CONNECTED :: False
DRO_DURATION :: 1
REWARD_TYPE :: pellet
REWARD_AMOUNT :: 1
DEBUG_WINDOW_ON :: True
Loaded monkey params
Screen loaded
743 clipart loaded in 0.471 seconds
pellet
pellet
User quit the program

Traceback (most recent call last):
  File "C:/Users/YLab/Downloads/ww_programs/rhesus-pygames/2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain_frontend.py", line 317, in <module>
    frontend.main()
  File "C:/Users/YLab/Downloads/ww_programs/rhesus-pygames/2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain_frontend.py", line 273, in main
    check_quit(event=event)
  File "C:\Users\YLab\Downloads\ww_programs\rhesus-pygames\2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain\MonkeyTrain\_modules\pgtools.py", line 153, in check_quit
    raise SystemExit
SystemExit

====================================================
     Date: 2021-08-26     Time: 11:45
====================================================
Loaded global params ::
SCREEN_W :: 1024
SCREEN_H :: 768
CURSOR_VISIBLE :: True
RESTRICT_SCREEN :: True
AUTOSHAPING :: True
TIME_TO_AUTOSHAPE :: 10
STIMULI_COLORS :: normal
HOST_CONNECTED :: True
RFID_READER_CONNECTED :: False
DRO_DURATION :: 1
REWARD_TYPE :: pellet
REWARD_AMOUNT :: 1
DEBUG_WINDOW_ON :: True
Loaded monkey params
Screen loaded
743 clipart loaded in 0.507 seconds
pellet
User quit the program

Traceback (most recent call last):
  File "C:/Users/YLab/Downloads/ww_programs/rhesus-pygames/2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain_frontend.py", line 317, in <module>
    frontend.main()
  File "C:/Users/YLab/Downloads/ww_programs/rhesus-pygames/2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain/MonkeyTrain_frontend.py", line 273, in main
    check_quit(event=event)
  File "C:\Users\YLab\Downloads\ww_programs\rhesus-pygames\2021.8.18-MonkeyTrain\MonkeyTrain\_modules\pgtools.py", line 153, in check_quit
    raise SystemExit
SystemExit

